fredericks.com 2011-05-18

# Privacy Policy

**_Privacy and Security_**

## Fredericks of Hollywood Privacy Policy

Frederick’s of Hollywood (“Frederick’s”) is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining a safe online experience for all of our users and customers while providing a quality user experience. Because we gather certain types of information about and from you, our users and customers, in order to fulfill your requests and better serve your needs, you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of this information. This Privacy Policy discloses what information we gather, how we use it, how to correct or change it, and what steps we take to safeguard personal information provided to us both online and offline. Please read the complete Privacy Policy below, as well as our Terms and Conditions of Use, and contact us if you have any questions.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU?**

You can visit our website at www.fredericks.com, browse our products and check on offerings without giving us any personally identifiable information. However, in order to provide users and customers with the most efficient and enhanced personalized service and attention, we may both request information about you in certain circumstances and collect certain information automatically. We also use contact lists and other information which are obtained from third parties. For the convenience of all of our customers and to better serve you, a customer account includes all the collected personal information we may have. Nevertheless, you can update or correct your contact information or change your preferences about receiving offers and information from third parties or us at any time.

**Information You Volunteer**

We collect personally identifiable information that you volunteer to us (such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, age, gender and/or similar demographic information), when you subscribe to our newsletters and special offers, place an order through our website (see the section below for more information on subscriptions and orders), or voluntarily register on our website. Website visitors may register to receive our e-mail updates. Registration may also be required to request a catalog or other information directly from us. Sometimes registration can be accomplished by submitting only a user name and password. In order to sign up for e-mail updates, all that is required is a name and valid e-mail address. However, in order to purchase our products online, we require the submission of additional information 

**Information Collected Automatically**

We may also automatically collect your IP and referring website addresses, browser type, domain name and website access times. This information helps facilitate your online experience on our website. We use cookies to track usage patterns on our website and to control the display of ads, as well as to offer other functionalities such as screening for age, helping to track items in your shopping basket, and “recognizing” you to speed up your log-in when you visit our website. You can turn off cookies, but that will affect your online experience. See below for more detail on cookies. 

**Other Information**

We conduct market research so that we can continually improve our brand and website and, in addition, we may purchase lists of potential users or customers from third parties. These lists may include information on current users or customers. This information is included in our database in order to help us serve you better by, for example, minimizing multiple mailings and e-mailings and providing information tailored to your interests.

**WHAT DO WE DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION?**

We use information you provide to fulfill your requests and improve our website, products and services. We may, from time to time, produce reports for advertisers, sponsors and vendors containing anonymous, aggregate information about our users and customers, such as demographic, age and online usage information. This information allows us to work closely with advertisers to provide content and offers that are most relevant to our users and customers. We do not include any personally identifiable information of our users in these reports.

We use personal information so that we may display or send custom, personalized content to our website visitors and send newsletters, mail, e-mails, features, promotional material, surveys and other updates, information or offers to our users and customers. A user may, at any time, opt out of receiving such information by following the procedures set forth below. We also use collected information to evaluate and administer our products and services, fulfill customer requests, respond to problems such as difficulties in navigating our websites or accessing certain features, and to gauge user trends to determine what products and services are most popular with users.

**HOW DO WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

Personal information is available to Frederick’s and the technical agents and consultants who make our website and products available to you. Anonymous information is available to our advertisers, sponsors and promotional and business partners. We share your personal information with third parties only as described below. 

**Frederick's and Its Agents.**

Frederick’s may access both anonymous, aggregate demographic data and any personal information you provide for internal marketing purposes, including sending you notices of new products. To facilitate subscriptions and orders, Frederick’s will cache your order information, and create an authorization with a merchant account (e.g., your credit card company). Website hosting firms, technical and database consultants and advertising agencies may have access to personally identifiable information in the course of making our products available to you. All companies working for and with Frederick’s must comply with our Privacy Policy, and are not permitted to sell or otherwise disclose your information to third parties except as authorized by us and you, or as permitted or required by law.

**Credit Card Companies.**

As in any transaction, your credit card company will have all relevant information about the name of the vendor, item(s) purchased, date, total cost and other information necessary to process the transaction. Frederick’s will not otherwise provide any personal data to your credit card company without your permission.

**Advertisers, Sponsors and Promotional and Business Partners.**

We may provide your personal and financial information to other reputable companies whose products or services might be of interest to you, if you provide prior consent to the exchange of such information. In addition, we share anonymous, aggregate demographic information, and anonymous information obtained from cookies and similar technologies, with our sponsors, promotional and business partners, and participating vendors. No personally identifiable information is disclosed to any of these third parties in providing these reports. Credit card numbers and passwords are not shared with advertisers, sponsors or promotional and business partners.

Information that we obtain in non-Internet transactions (i.e., in our retail stores) is handled differently. We may share offline contact information with third parties, who may send you offers or information about their products or services. You must opt-out if you do not wish to receive information from third parties or us by mail.

Your e-mail address is not shared with third parties unless you agree to receive information, by opting-in, from third parties. In other words, we may extend e-mail offers to users or customers on behalf of our business partners about a particular product or service that may be of interest to you, but only if you have indicated that you would like to receive these offers. If you wish to receive such offers, we will not share or disclose your name or e-mail address to those business partners, but will send you the information or offers on their behalf. As result, although Frederick’s may receive a fee from our business partners for this service, Frederick’s sends the offers so that your personal information is never shared with any outside third party. Of course, you may opt out of receiving these offers at any time. 

Sometimes we will give you the opportunity to opt in to receive e-mail offers from third parties not affiliated with Frederick’s. If you decide to accept these offers, we will provide, with your consent, your contact information to the third party. We urge visitors to review carefully the privacy policies of these firms. Frederick’s is not responsible for the privacy policies and procedures of any third party. 

You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information, personal or otherwise, online in any community area, that information can be collected and used by others. For example, if you use chat, forums, bulletin boards or message boards, or if you post personal information online (such as your e-mail address), you may receive unsolicited messages from others. Frederick’s has no control over this use of your personal information.

**Important Note**

We reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent for the following purposes: as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request; to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our website and our property; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfill your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation.

**HOW DO WE USE COOKIES?**

Your web browser offers so-called “cookies” which, if you allow their use, store small amounts of data on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify you personally. However, cookies assist us in tracking which of our features you like best. For example, cookies allow us to know that the person who added the Hollywood Exxtreme Cleavage® Bra to their basket is the same person as the one who wants the marabou baby doll. Therefore, cookies enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser and our website is viewable even if you disable the cookie function on your browser. However, if you disable cookies, some advanced and customized features or offerings will not be available to you. 

**HOW DO WE USE WEB BEACONS?**

Some of our website pages may contain electronic images known as web beacons, which are also called “single-pixel gifs”. These images allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We also may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to count how many messages have been opened and acted upon. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information but they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our website usage. Web beacons collect only a limited range of information, including the time and date of page view, cookie number and description of the page on which the web beacon resides. 

**HOW CAN YOU CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

We believe that choice in how and when you are contacted is key to customer satisfaction. Therefore, we offer several ways for you to update your contact information and/or change your preferences.

  1. If you have an online account at our website, you may be able to log on and update or change your contact or account information. Check the website for further information.
  2. If you do not have an account, you can also unsubscribe via our website at the following URL: <http://www.fredericks.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-FoH-Site/default/Page-EmailUnsubscribe>.
  3. You may unsubscribe to any of our online e-mail updates by following the unsubscribe instructions in the body of any e-mail message. 
  4. You may write to us and update your contact information or ask that we not share your personal contact information with third parties at: Frederick’s of Hollywood, Inc., c/o Customer Service Department, P.O. Box 2949, Phoenix, AZ 85062-2949. In those instances, we will retain your information in a “do not promote” file in our database. 
  5. You may also contact us at custserv@fredericks.com.

We will take commercially reasonable steps to implement your opt-out requests promptly, but you may still receive promotional information from us by mail for up to 60 days due to printing and mailing schedules, and up to 10 days for e-mail. You may also continue to receive information from those third parties to whom your information was previously disclosed.

**SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt important information, such as your credit card data, in an effort to prevent unauthorized access during transmission of your orders over the Internet. We incorporate standard industry practices internally and with our service providers, which we believe suits the degree of sensitivity of the information involved to maintain the security of your personal information and to avoid its disclosure except as described in this Privacy Policy. Your personal information may also be protected by the password you created when you registered at our website where this feature is offered. The confidentiality of any password is yours to protect. You may change it at anytime by following the instructions on the website. 

Although we have implemented systems and procedures to secure the data maintained by us, security during Internet transmissions can never be assured. Frederick’s employees are made aware of our privacy practices through periodic communications and training. Our policy is to limit access to personal data to those Frederick’s employees or agents with a specific need to access or retrieve this information. We store data on multiple service systems, in controlled environments. To maintain security, we conduct internal reviews of our security measures on a regular basis. Remember, however, that any personal information you post in chat rooms or message boards is available to anyone.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

Frederick's is strongly committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children who visit our websites. We do not knowingly collect personal information online from children under 13 and have adopted techniques to age-screen users on our teen-oriented websites to ensure compliance with this Privacy Policy and the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying regulations under United States federal law protect the privacy of children using the Internet. Our website includes content that we believe to be unsuitable for children under 13 and which are not necessarily monitored. We encourage all parents to talk to their children about online safety and to monitor their children's use of the Internet.

**CHANGES IN CORPORATE STRUCTURE**

In developing our business, we may engage in the sale of certain assets and the company itself, or parts of it, may be sold, merged or otherwise transferred. In such transactions and changes in ownership, user information, whether personally identifiable or otherwise, may constitute one of the transferred assets. Frederick's will notify affected users in accordance with the procedure for changing this Privacy Policy described below.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We update this Privacy Policy as we believe is necessary to protect our users and to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the Privacy Policy when you visit our website to be sure that you are aware of and understand our current policy. If we make material changes to this policy, or in how we use or collect your personally identifiable information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We will not make any retroactive material changes in how we handle previously collected personal information unless you allow us to do so, or unless we are legally required to do so, and in such a case we will e-mail registered website visitors information on material changes to this Privacy Policy. 

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information Frederick’s shares with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates’ direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Frederick’s of Hollywood, Inc., Customer Service Department, P.O. Box 2949, Phoenix, AZ 85062-2949. In your request, please include your postal address and specify that you want a “Your Frederick’s California Privacy Rights Notice”. Please allow at least 30 days for a response. 

**CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please use our [contact feedback form](http://www.fredericks.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-FoH-Site/default/Page-ContactUs "Contact Us").

> Or you can contact us by mail at:   
>  Frederick’s of Hollywood, Inc.   
>  Customer Service Department  
>  P.O. Box 2949  
>  Phoenix, AZ 85062-2949
> 
> Updated October, 2008
